Finding Aid for Carol T. Mowbray papers, 1973-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Carol T. Mowbray papers
1973-2006
Mowbray, Carol T.
06138 Aa 2
Professor at the University of Michigan School of Social Work; was heavily involved in researching psychosocial rehabilitation of the mentally ill and an advocate of supported education; and researched the affects of mental illness on mothers. Collection consists of correspondence, lectures and speeches, project information and publications completed during her tenure at the University of Michigan and Wayne State University
11.6 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Donated July 3, 2006 (Donor no. 9767 )
No further additions are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Carol T. Mowbray earned a bachelor's degree in psychology and mathematics from Tufts University, and her doctorate in developmental psychology from the University of Michigan. She served as an evaluator at the Michigan Department of Mental Health (MDMH) and for almost a decade was the Director of Research and Demonstration Projects for the Bureau of Program Development and Quality Assurance. She was an Associate Professor at the Wayne State University School of Social Work, and a Professor of Ecological/Community Psychology at Michigan State University. In 1994 she joined the University of Michigan School of Social Work (SSW) as a professor and from 1996-2001 was the SSW Associate Dean of Research.
Mowbray was a prolific author, writing more than 130 scientific articles, chapters and books. She focused on the psychosocial rehabilitation of adults with mental illness, especially homeless populations and those with substance-abuse problems. She developed and evaluated the effectiveness of intervention strategies for mentally ill persons, emphasizing consumer-run and supported education programs. She also developed a specialization in women with mental illness and how it affected motherhood and raising children.
The Carol T. Mowbray collection consists primarily of correspondence and project related materials and publications detailing her professional career. This collection is divided into eight series: Personal, Correspondence, Teaching, Conferences, Lectures and Speeches, Committees, Projects and Publications. The collection is organized primarily in alphabetical or chronological order for ease of use. The collection itself is focused on the professional activities of Carol T. Mowbray, and researchers will find few insights into the personal life and character of Carol outside of the work environment.
Subjects:
Mowbray, Carol T.; University of Michigan. School of Social Work.; Mental illness.
- Personal, 1990-2005
  The Personal series (0.2 linear feet) contains letters of appreciation, Curriculum Vitas, awards and newsclippings. The Curriculum Vitas are notable for their thoroughness and comprehensiveness.
  - Awards, 1998; 2000 (Box 1)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 2002-2005 (Box 1)
  - Job Transitions, 1990-1995; 2004 (Box 1)
  - Letters of Appreciation, 1996-2004 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1992-2004 (Box 1)
  - Newsclippings, 1995; 2000 (Box 1)
  - Schedule, 1996; 1999 (Box 1)
  - Who's Who, 1994-2003 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1990-2005
  The Correspondence series (1.3 linear feet) consists of correspondence between Mowbray and members of the various organizations and committees of which he was a part. The letters were originally organized in 3-ring binders according to month and year. The letters have been removed from the binders, but retain the same order and separators as before. These letters span all aspects of her work including projects, publications and teaching.
  - August 1990-December 1990 (Box 1)
  - January 1991-April 1991 (Box 1)
  - May 1991-August 1991 (Box 1)
  - September 1991-January 1992 (Box 1)
  - February 1992-June 1992 (Box 1)
  - July 1992-December 1992 (Box 1)
  - January 1993-May 1993 (Box 1)
  - June 1993-October 1993 (Box 1)
  - November 1993-January 1994 (Box 1)
  - February 1994-July 1994 (Box 1)
  - August 1994-December 1994 (Box 1)
  - January 1995-July 1995 (Box 1)
  - August 1995-March 1996 (Box 1)
  - April 1996-December 1996 (Box 1)
  - December 1996-July 1997 (Box 2)
  - August 1997-February 1998 (Box 2)
  - March -- July 1998 (Box 2)
  - August 1998-January 1999 (Box 2)
  - February 1999-December 2000 (Box 2)
  - January 2001-February 2002 (Box 2)
  - March 2002-January 2003 (Box 2)
  - February 2003-October 2004 (Box 2)
  - November 2004-June 2005 (Box 2)
- Teaching, 1974-2005
  The Teaching series (1.0 linear feet) consists of annual reports, class syllabi and lecture notes, as well as teaching evaluations. The annual reports are very thorough and are great snap-shots of Carol's work in an individual year. Her teaching activities have been divided up by class taught and where applicable into syllabi and lectures.
  - Annual Reports, 1995-2005; 14 folders (Box 2)
  - Consumer Narratives and Analysis, 1997-2000 (Box 2)
  - Endowment Program on Mental Health, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Planned Research Activities at Wayne State University, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Promotion Application to Full Professor, 1999-2000 (Box 2)
  - Psychology 655-Psychology of Women, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Psychology 970-Advanced Topics in Mental Health Services, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Sabbatical Report, 2002 (Box 2)
  - School of Social Work
    - Faculty Retreat, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Life Sciences Initiative, 1999-2000 (Box 2)
  - Seminar on Women, Mental Health and Illness, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Social Work 631-Research Methods for Evaluating Social Programs and Human Services Organizations, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Social Work 670-Analytic Methods for Social Policy Practice, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Social Work 682-Evaluation in Macropractice
    - Computer Lab Notes, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Syllabus, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Social Work 682/685-Problem Sets, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Social Work 685-Advanced Evaluation Methods, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Social Work 691-Women's Issues Seminar, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Social Work 691-Women's Psychosocial Functioning, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Social Work 756-Human Behavior in the Social Environment
    - Lecture-"Developmental Theories, undated (Box 3)
    - Lecture-"Families of the Mentally Ill", undated (Box 3)
    - Lecture-"The History of Childhood", undated (Box 3)
    - Lecture-"Plagetian Theory", undated (Box 3)
    - Lecture-"Social Networks and Social Support", undated (Box 3)
    - Lecture-"Theories of Mental Illness-Internationalist Perspectives", undated (Box 3)
    - Lecture-"Violence and Children", undated (Box 3)
    - Lecture-"Writing Articles for Publication", 1992 (Box 3)
    - Lectures and Course Materials, undated (Box 3)
    - Syllabi and Assignments, 1991-1993; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Social Work 766-Human Behavior in the Social Environment II, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Social Work 782-Research Methods, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Social Work 812-Prevention Research, 2003-2005; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Social Work 819-Mental Health Service Utilization: Predictors & Problems, November 2004 (Box 3)
  - Social Work 819-Promoting Well-Being: Poverty, Race-Ethnicity & Mental Health, 2002; 1 zip disks (Box 3)
  - Social Work 831-Program Evaluation, 1999; 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 3)
  - Social Work 831-Program Evaluation, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Social Work 843-Seminar on Poverty, Risk and Mental Health, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Social Work 843-Seminar on Poverty, Risk and Mental Health, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Social Work 860-Program Theory, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Social Work 860-Translational Skills, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Social Work Research Seminar, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Teaching Evaluations, 1994-2005 (Box 3)
  - Tenure Application, 1993-1994 (Box 3)
- Conferences, 1977-2005
  The Conferences series (1.3 linear feet) contains programs, applications and presentations delivered at various conferences she attended. She was largely involved in the International Association of Psychosocial Rehabilitation Services (IAPSRS), American Evaluation Association (AEA) and the American Psychological Association (APA) conferences.
  - American Evaluation Association, 2003-2005; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - American Psychological Association, (APA), 1992; 1998-2004; 8 folders (Box 3)
  - Assertive Community Treatment Conference, 1999 (Box 3)
  - CASE Media Workshop, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Center for Psychiatric Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Center for Psychiatric Rehabilitation, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Community Based Work, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Community Integration: Every Single One, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Depression on College Campuses, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Evaluation for Community Mental Health, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Evaluation for Practice, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Facilitating Careers for Mental Health Consumers, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post Secondary Education, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Group for the Advancement of Doctoral Education, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Social Work Research, 2004 (Box 3)
  - International Association of Psychosocial Rehabilitation Services (IAPSRS), 1993; 1998-2004; 9 folders (Box 4)
  - IAPSRS Workshop-Project WINS, 1994 (Box 4)
  - International Conference on Research for Social Work Practice, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Lansing Forum, March 2003 (Box 4)
  - Louis de la Parte Florida Mental Health Conference, April 1998 (Box 4)
  - Matrix Conference, October 2000 (Box 4)
  - Mental Health Research in Michigan, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
  - Michigan Association for Evaluation, 1999-2000; 2003; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Michigan Association for Infant Mental Health, May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Michigan Association of Community Mental Health, 1994; 1998; 2000 (Box 4)
  - Michigan Association of Community Mental Health Boards, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Michigan Association on Higher Education and Disability, May 2002 (Box 4)
  - Michigan Chapters of the Alliance for the Mentally Ill and the IAPSRS, December 1998 (Box 4)
  - Michigan Chapter of the National Association of Social Workers, 1998; 2000; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Michigan IAPSRS, 2000-2001; 2003; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Michigan's Future: Investing in our Families and Children, December 1989 (Box 4)
  - National Advisory Group on Parents with Psychiatric Disorders and their Families, October 1999 (Box 4)
  - NAMI Wisconsin Convention, June 1999 (Box 4)
  - National Association for Mental Illness (NAMI), June 2003 (Box 4)
  - NASMHPD Research Conference, 1993 (Box 4)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), April-June, 2002 (Box 4)
  - NIMH-Perinatal Mood Disorders, July 2002 (Box 4)
  - New York State Office of Mental Health, November 1997 (Box 4)
  - Psychiatric Rehabilitation Educator's Symposium, October 2003 (Box 4)
  - SAMHSA, December 1997 (Box 4)
  - SfAA, March 2000 (Box 4)
  - Sharpening Our Focus: The Second Supported Education Conference, October 2003 (Box 4)
  - Shifting the Lens: A National Supported Education Conference, April 2000 (Box 4)
  - Society for Social Work and Research, 1999-2005; 7 folders (Box 4)
  - Supported Education Conference, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Symposium on Protecting Client's Rights, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Team for the Assessment of Psychiatric Services, July 1997 (Box 4)
  - US Psychiatric Rehabilitation Association, May 2005 (Box 4)
  - University of North Carolina, December 2004 (Box 4)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation Research Colloquium, April 1996 (Box 4)
  - World Association for Psychiatric Rehabilitation, August 2003 (Box 4)
- Lectures and Speeches, 1985-2004
  The Lectures and Speeches (0.6 linear feet) series comprises materials from various lectures, workshops, and symposiums where Mowbray spoke. This series includes lectures on writing for publishing, dual diagnosis, research ethics and mental illness stigmas.
  - Bioethics Seminar, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Child Sexual Abuse Research Project, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Conflict of Interest Seminar, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Dual Diagnosis, 1990-1992 (Box 4)
  - Evaluation Focus Groups, undated (Box 5)
  - Evaluation Research Designs, undated (Box 5)
  - Evaluation Utilization, 1988-1991; 1998 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Discussion on Authorship Credit, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Workshop, "Writing for Publication", 1999 (Box 5)
  - Grant Writing Workshop, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Homeless Services, undated (Box 5)
  - Involuntary Outpatient Commitment, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
  - Lessons Learned from a Homeless/Demo Project, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Longitudinal Research and Tracking Methods, undated (Box 5)
  - Managed Care, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health Data from the National Center for Health Statistics, May 2000 (Box 5)
  - Methodological Challenges in Evaluating Services to Homeless Mentally Ill Adults, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Needs Assessment, Mental Health Planning and Evaluation, 1988-1991 (Box 5)
  - O/V Evaluation and Logic Models, May 2004 (Box 5)
  - The Process of Resubmission to the NIH, April 1996 (Box 5)
  - Program Fidelity, 2001-2004 (Box 5)
  - Psychiatric Rehabilitation, undated (Box 5)
  - The Recovery Perspective: Mental Health and Mental Illness Services in the 21st Century, November 2003 (Box 5)
  - Research Ethics-General Lecture, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
  - Research Responsibility Program-Authorship in the Social Sciences, October 1999; October 2000 (Box 5)
  - The Shirley Thrasher Memorial, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Social Work and Psychiatry Spring Lecture, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Social Work Student Orientation, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Speeches on Homeless Michigan, 1989-1993 (Box 5)
  - Stigma and Mental Illness: From the Perspective of the Stigmatized, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Washtenaw Integrated Health Care Project, January 2000 (Box 5)
- Committees, 1983-2005
  The Committees series (0.8 linear feet) contains materials relevant to committees Mowbray served on. Included in this series are committees within the School of Social Work at the University of Michigan, American Psychological Association and the Action Committee for Women.
  - Action Committee for Women
    - Childcare Information Guide, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Evaluation Questionnaire, 1987 (Box 5)
    - For Better or Worse? Women and the Mental Health System, 1983 (Box 5)
    - For the Better, 1986-1989 (Box 5)
    - History and Annual Report, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Improving Clinical Services to Women, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 5)
    - Services to Chronically Mentally Ill Women, 1985 (Box 5)
    - Services to Chronically Mentally Ill Women Conference Proceedings, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Special Populations: Problems and Perspectives, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Women and Mental Health: New Directions for Change, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Women at Work Conference, 1986 (Box 5)
  - American Psychological Association
    - Committee on Women in Psychology, 1999-2004 (Box 5)
    - Division 18-Executive Committee, 1995; 2001 (Box 5)
    - Division 27-Fellows Committee, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Division 27-Fellowship Committee, 1988-2004 (Box 5)
    - Division 35-Consumer Committee, 1986-1991 (Box 5)
    - Stigma Subcommittee, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
    - Task Force on Serious Mental Illness, 1999-2004 (Box 5)
  - Center for Mental Health Services and Criminal Justice Research, 2005 (Box 5)
  - Center for Psychiatric Rehabilitation's Advisory Council, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Department of Community Health-Evidence Based Practice Subcommittee, 2004-2005 (Box 5)
  - Detroit-Wayne County-Community Mental Health Research Advisory Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
  - GIS Workgroup for the National Institute for Mental Health (NIMH) Center, 2002-2003 (Box 5)
  - The Grand Rounds Series, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - IAPSRS (Michigan Chapter)-Board of Directors, 1997-2001 (Box 5)
  - IAPSRS Research Committee, 2000-2005 (Box 5)
  - IAPSRS Research Committee-Toolkit Final Report, 1997 (Box 5)
  - IAPSRS Workshop Committee, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health Services Research Group, 2000-2001 (Box 5)
  - OVPR Conflict of Interest Review Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 5)
  - R&T Center's Advisory Committee, 1995-1999 (Box 5)
  - School of Social Work (Box 6)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Adjunct Faculty, 1999-2000 (Box 6)
    - Communications Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 6)
    - Facilities Advisory Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Mental Health Curriculum Committee, 2000-2004 (Box 6)
    - Multicultural and Gender Affairs Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 6)
    - Policy and Evaluation Work Group, 2004-2005 (Box 6)
    - Recruitment, Admissions and Financial Aid Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 6)
  - Technical Expert Group on Women with Serious Mental Illness as Mothers, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Underrepresented Minority Research Fellowship Advisory Committee, 2000-2002 (Box 6)
  - University of Michigan Depression Center Steering Committee
    - Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 2001-2005 (Box 6)
    - Manual, circa 2004 (Box 6)
    - Minutes and Agendas, 2001-2005 (Box 6)
- Projects, 1986-2005
  The Projects series (4.2 linear feet) is the largest series in this collection. It is organized by project title and further subdivided where necessary. Included in these files are project descriptions, meeting minutes, data, reports and proposals. The projects series should be reviewed in tandem with the appropriate project-related publications to provide a full picture of Carol Mowbray's findings and her conclusions.
  - Ann Arbor Downtown Homeless Shelter Project, 1999-2001 (Box 6)
  - Assertive Community Treatment
    - Grant Application, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Draft Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Center for Research on Poverty, Risk, and Mental Illness
    - Correspondence, 1996-2005; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1996-1998 (Box 6)
    - Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 2002-2005 (Box 6)
    - Notes and Miscellaneous, 1996-2004; undated (Box 6)
    - Reports and Administrative Papers, 1996-1998; undated (Box 6)
    - Reports and Administrative Papers, 2002-2004 (Box 6)
  - Community Foundation of Southeastern Michigan, 1997-1999 (Box 6)
  - Consulting, 1993; 1997-2003; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Consumer Education, 1999 (Box 6)
  - CSP-WINS Grant Proposal (unfunded), 1990-1993 (Box 6)
  - Detroit Compact School-Based Human Services
    - Data and Surveys, 1994-1996; undated (Box 6)
    - Evaluation Report, 1996; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Meeting Notes, 1993-1996 (Box 6)
    - Project Administration, 1994-1996; undated (Box 6)
    - School Observations, 1993-1995 (Box 6)
  - Developing Centers for Interventions and Services Research, 2002 (Box 6)
  - Development Center-Suicide Prevention, 2003-2004 (Box 6)
  - Empowerment Evaluation, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Enhancing Vocational Opportunities
    - Contract, 1992-1994 (Box 6)
    - Expenses, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Five-Year Follow-up Study of Supported Education, 1998-2002 (Box 7)
  - GLASER (Great Lakes Supported Education Replication)
    - Final Evaluation Survey Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 7)
    - Grant Proposal, 2000; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Project Directors Meeting, May 2003 (Box 7)
    - Site Observations, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Teleconferences, 2001 (Box 7)
  - Graduate Student Research Assistanceships, 1995-2003 (Box 7)
  - Grand Rapids Peer Support
    - Interviews, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Notes, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Reports, undated (Box 7)
  - Homeless in Michigan Demonstration Project, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Kalamazoo Center of Mental Health Supported Education Consultation, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Letters for Project Support (Written by Carol Mowbray), 1994-1995; 2003-2005 (Box 7)
  - M-COIT Project, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Mental Health Prevention Research Training Program, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Mentality
    - Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1998-2004 (Box 7)
    - Evaluation Research, 2001-2004 (Box 7)
    - Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1999-2004 (Box 7)
    - Non-Fiction Writing Project, 2004-2005 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Group Home Research Project
    - Client Data, 1986-1988 (Box 7)
    - Final Report, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Resident Assessment Package, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Staff Notes, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Parents Survey, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Rehabilitation Services/SE-CAG Grant, 2000; 2004 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Supported Education Program
    - Follow-up Study-Data and Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
    - Outcomes, undated (Box 7)
    - Proposals for Funding, 1994-1999 (Box 7)
    - Questionnaires and Data, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH) State Planning Study, January 1987; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Parental Preference for Sex of Children in the US, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Pilot Multi-Site Study of Supported Education, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Project MOMS, 2000-2004 (Box 8)
  - Project WINS (Work Interest and Needs Study)
    - Budgets, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
    - Data Sets, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
    - Expense Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 8)
    - Final Report, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Follow up Study Data Analysis, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
    - Grant Application, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Interviewer's Manual, 1992; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1990-1995; 1999; 4 folders (Box 8)
    - Peer Support Specialist Focus Groups, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
    - Research Data, 1992-1994 (Box 8)
    - Staff Reassignment, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
    - Steve Leff Site Visit, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Supplemental Study, 1993-1995 (Box 8)
  - Proposal Reviews
    - "Low Income Mothers With and Without Psychiatric Disability", 2000 (Box 8)
    - Ontario Mental Health Foundation, 1998 (Box 8)
  - "Psychosocial Outcomes for Adult Children of SMI Mothers", 2003 (Box 8)
  - RISP-Guidance Center Meeting, March 2005 (Box 8)
  - Substance Abuse and Mental Illness (SAMI) Study
    - Baseline Description and Subgame Differences, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Competing Renewal, 1994 (Box 8)
    - Continuation Grant, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Data Analysis, 1995-1996 (Box 8)
    - Data Codes and Resident Stability Outcomes, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Grant and Research Design Notes, 1990-1992 (Box 8)
    - Longitudinal Study Grant, 1994 (Box 8)
    - Meeting Notes, 1990-1993 (Box 8)
    - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1994-1996 (Box 9)
    - Michigan Department of Mental Health Contract, 1994 (Box 9)
    - One-Year Continuation Grant, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Patterns of Change Scores, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Project Correspondence, 1999; 2003 (Box 9)
    - Project Manual and Interviewer Manual, October 1992; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Research Procedures and Documents, 1990-1993 (Box 9)
    - Tracking Methods and Results, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Women's Supplement, undated (Box 9)
  - SE-CAG (Supported Education-Community Action Grant)
    - Grant Application, 1997; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Manuals, Timeline, and Session Agendas, 1998 (Box 9)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1998-2004; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Needs and Resource Assessment, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Phase II Grant Proposal, 1999; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 9)
    - Retreat, September 1999 (Box 9)
    - Surveys and Needs Assessment Reports, 1998-2001 (Box 9)
    - Training Session, November 30, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Training Session, February 18, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Training Session, June 23, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Training Session, May 5, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Supported Education
    - A Comparison of Three Approaches to Supported Education, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1995-2005 (Box 9)
    - Cost Survey and Program Data, 2000-2002 (Box 9)
    - News Clippings and Stories, 1995-1998 (Box 9)
    - R-01 Submission, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Vocational Research Group, 1992-1995 (Box 9)
  - Washtenaw Community Health Organization, 2001-2003 (Box 9)
  - Washtenaw County Integrated Health Care Project, 1998-2000 (Box 9)
  - Washtenaw Integrated Health Care Project (Box 10)
    - Agendas and Schedules, 2000-2001 (Box 10)
    - Focus Group Materials, 1998-2000 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Washtenaw-Genesee Homeless Project
    - Case Studies and Data, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Contracts, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence and Notes, 1990-2003; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Evaluation Design, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Final Reports, 1993 (Box 10)